[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What was the greatest part?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I've been to so many.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Welcome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "You don't really take prisoners, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Is there a theme that you see in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I never thought of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "She's in her 90s, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "And she's been like most mothers -- she's been your biggest fan and critic over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "She thinks so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "The good stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kevin Costner", "Anthony Hopkins"]}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Which of all the actors you've worked with has been the best?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Kevin Costner is as different from Anthony Hopkins as night to day, but they are both extraordinary to work with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Charlie Sheen was a young man when I worked with him on two films.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'80s"]}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "But what did you feel, looking at this guy, who you'd worked so closely with before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I lost track of Charlie in the mid-'80s, late '80s.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 149, "question": "In the old days, in the old days, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I mean, taking --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Downey"]}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "All of you at your peak, who would be the greatest guest, you'd have to a party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Robert Downey was pretty wild.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "What is the simplistic answer, do you think, to the global drugs problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "It's not going to go away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNP", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "And it hasn't worked, has it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "And the U.S. -- and the Mexican economy would die without it because they need the money, it goes into their legitimate economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":", "MD", "VB", "RB", ":", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "-- what do you do?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "If you killed the -- if you declared -- if there were no war on drugs, the Mexican economy would have to -- would be radically -- would dry up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Do you ever wish you hadn't done that particular scene, the greed is good scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "-- took it at face value, didn't they?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Couldn't believe it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Are they effective?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Some are, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "``"], "qSentId": 285, "question": "When you see your country, $16 trillion in debt and everyone's squabbling over what most people say, is an insubstantial solution, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "RBS", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Oh!", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$16 trillion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "And do you think it would help if more policy makers in America had experienced war?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What was it you learned about yourself, when you were in Vietnam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, first of all I learned to survive.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "I think your theme about war, generally, throughout all of your movies, is incredibly important, actually?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "CC", ":", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I'm not going to give away ending but -- because that's a spoiler --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "I think it's hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "You've tried it lately, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Just from what you said about her!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "She comes from a totally different world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "If you were describing yourself to somebody, who had never heard anything about you, what would be the honest description?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I'm equally astonished and disappointed by myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Why astonished?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Put it this way, I think this life is a mystery and it's also a hunt for the truth, a hunt for what works for you and you express yourself as you go, sometimes badly, sometimes well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Why disappointed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "In the same way because, gosh!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN"], "qSentId": 437, "question": "I would say -- I mean, yes, I mean, if it's -- you can jazz up it a bit, can't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "No!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "That's simple descriptive word, filmmaker, would be enough for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Dramatist, if you want or, you know, but that sums it up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Nothing personal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "He was a good citizen, I hope!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How are you, sir?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "This teddy bear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "How do you break their little hearts and say they can't go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "I told them that the bear has a potty mouth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What's her name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "White trash name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Wait, was it any one of those names with a \"Lynn\" after it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "You just came in and went -- is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "VBD", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Did you get it right every time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "OK, how?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "A lot of practice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Any names?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Yeah, plenty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Russell Crowe"]}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Who are the ones you look at and go, that's where I want to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "VB", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Russell Crowe is extremely prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Do you like that versatility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Can you do that accent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Would you be the mentor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yes, unfortunately, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "When you look back over this amazing career you've had, with all the twists and turns, if I had the power to let you relive one moment again, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I would probably choose not quitting school because that's when everything started to go downhill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "What did she say about you doing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "She's very proud me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "What have you found you're good at and not so good at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "I'm very good at math.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Counting money, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Your mother must find it extraordinary, what's happened to you, doesn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Are these friends of yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Yeah, we're friendly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Was there a moment, a cathartic moment, where you just woke up and went, I'm done with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "Certainly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Did you have a red devil on your shoulder that whispers in your ear occasionally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "No temptation to suddenly go crazy again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "That gives you enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Is it because you know where you came from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "Where are you sitting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "I'm going to go down and pull the lever, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Were you there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "No, I was not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Not invited?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "No, I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "You even turned down dinner with the president and George Clooney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "You know, you can cut a check and go.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Clooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 834, "question": "It was such a great role, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 835, "answer": "I was nervous about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "When you are in the Jacuzzi, semi-naked with Burt Reynolds, fun or awkward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "A bit awkward.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Burt Reynolds"], "LOCATION": ["Jacuzzi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "Is he a good guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "He's a great guy, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "CD", "TO", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "ORGAN: Sorry, give it to me again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "One sixty five to 205, 45.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120629pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "It comes out the weekend, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]